<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <title>Kourken Kasbarian - Blog</title>
  
  <subtitle>Kourken Kasbarian - Blog</subtitle>
  <link href="/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  
  <link href="http://blog.kkasbarian.com/"/>
  <updated>2018-02-05T15:03:27.262Z</updated>
  <id>http://blog.kkasbarian.com/</id>
  
  <author>
    <name>Kourken Kasbarian</name>
    
  </author>
  
  <generator uri="http://hexo.io/">Hexo</generator>
  
  <entry>
    <title>My 30Days30Sites Challenge Journey</title>
    <link href="http://blog.kkasbarian.com/2018/02/my-journey-of-the-30days30sites-challenge/"/>
    <id>http://blog.kkasbarian.com/2018/02/my-journey-of-the-30days30sites-challenge/</id>
    <published>2018-02-05T15:00:00.000Z</published>
    <updated>2018-02-05T15:03:27.262Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<div class="flex-share-btn"><br>    <div class="fb-share-button" data-href="http://blog.kkasbarian.com/2018/02/my-journey-of-the-30days30sites-challenge/" data-layout="button_count" data-size="small" data-mobile-iframe="true"><a class="fb-xfbml-parse-ignore" target="_blank" href="https://www.facebook.com/sharer/sharer.php?u=http%3A//blog.kkasbarian.com/2018/02/my-journey-of-the-30days30sites-challenge/">Share</a></div><br>    <div><a class="twitter-share-button" href="https://twitter.com/intent/tweet" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Tweet</a></div><br>    <div><a class="twitter-follow-button" data-show-count="false" href="https://twitter.com/KourkenK" target="_blank" rel="noopener"> Follow @KourkenK</a></div><br></div><p>Read Time: 7 min read</p><h1 id="Introduction"><a href="#Introduction" class="headerlink" title="Introduction:"></a>Introduction:</h1><p>Nowadays, lots of people, be it students, university students (including me), a person who wants to change his career or just as a hobby, start to learn Web Development. They start to learn the basics, for example HTML and CSS by watching videos, following some tutorials or even by a book, but after few weeks of learning, when they want to get their hands dirty to code, they feel lost, they can’t make a simple website and they feel frustrated. Some even have the intention to quit after this. 😕</p><p>The thing is, you can not only rely on a tutorial and make a professional website after, it’s <strong>Ok</strong> to watch videos and tutorials, play with the source code provided, but you should not spend most of your time on those videos. You should make some projects (or side projects, per se) on your own, be it a simple ‘Hello World’ title on a blank page, a few sections or even multiple paged websites.</p><hr class="post-hr"><h1 id="Side-Projects"><a href="#Side-Projects" class="headerlink" title="Side Projects?!"></a>Side Projects?!</h1><div class="pic-center"><br><img src="https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/800/1*h1gbqI6vuwaoC3Ccmo3_sw.jpeg" alt="Coding is passion"><br>Coding is passion<br></div><p>Beginners would think, what is a side project? Why you need those side projects? 🤔 Well, you should first get the hang of the technologies that you want to learn, after that, you should make a decent <em>portfolio</em> website in order to showcase your work and even make a <em>resume</em> while you get more comfortable so when you apply for a job, you have already made some projects that the recruiter or the employer will check. It’s better than to have nothing to show, not even a portfolio, how will they know that you have the knowledge enough to hire you!</p><p class="quote">“Always practice, learn, code and build something, that’s the way to go further in web development!!” — Me</p><p>I myself had to go into some of the struggles that I mentioned at first when I started, I had no idea what kind of projects to build, the next <em><strong>Facebook</strong></em>? No, that’s hard (Really Hard!!). A portfolio for myself? Umm, I don’t have any projects and I don’t know what to write about my knowledge!! These were few stuff that I was thinking when I wanted to code something but I couldn’t.</p><p>I also did some basic projects locally just to test my knowledge, which were not that good. I wrote an article about this and my journey to start as a Front-End Web Developer, you can check it out from my personal blog <a href="http://blog.kkasbarian.com/2017/09/my-web-dev-journey/"><strong>here</strong></a> or on Medium <a href="https://medium.com/@kourkenkasbarian/how-i-started-my-web-development-journey-cc7e9e40b58d" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><strong>here</strong></a>.</p><p>I searched for projects to do, some were hard, I also saw that people are into some challenges, for example, 300daysofcode or 100daysofcode and I was thinking, wow, these people are really advanced that they’re coding every day, and have milestones etc. but suddenly I see a project somewhere from someone which was tagged by 30days30sites tag and few others which drew my attention. 😮</p><p>I thought, what this challenge is about? How someone can build a site in one day. But hey, I wanted to build websites anyway, so this seemed to be what I wanted. I applied and started getting the prompt emails in the next days.</p><hr class="post-hr"><h1 id="So-what’s-the-30Days30Sites-Challenge"><a href="#So-what’s-the-30Days30Sites-Challenge" class="headerlink" title="So, what’s the 30Days30Sites Challenge?"></a>So, what’s the 30Days30Sites Challenge?</h1><div class="pic-center"><br><img src="https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/800/1*nQGSndQrcHzk0M8FZZmpHQ.jpeg" alt="30Days30Sites Twitter Page"><br>30Days30Sites Twitter Page<br></div><p>Basically, it’s an awesome challenge, you get a prompt email every day for 30 days, first it mentions what kind of website you should build, followed by some instructions, then there is a ‘demo’ website for that particular kind of site and a handy tutorial about something related to Web Development which could help you while building the websites or at least get some knowledge.</p><p>This means that you have the topic of the website, and your imagination is the limit on how you should make the look and feel of the website, the content, colors, you name it, even the technologies that you can use. There are no restrictions.</p><hr class="post-hr"><h1 id="The-Process"><a href="#The-Process" class="headerlink" title="The Process:"></a>The Process:</h1><div class="pic-center"><br><img src="https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/800/1*fMV93odOMr_xK0Djsx_dTw.jpeg" alt="29th Site getting built"><br>29th Site getting built<br></div><p>The actual process is the most important but at the same time, the most interesting part of this challenge. You start planning, looking at some other websites as an inspiration, getting the text editor ready, grab the images, links, tools and libraries (if needed) that are necessary for the project and get your hands finally dirty!! 💻</p><p>As you start the challenge, you might think that getting a site ready in one day isn’t possible or as a minimum it won’t be “<em>cool</em>”, well, no problem, do it in few days (no more than a week though!!). You might also think that a framework like Bootstrap will make your life easier, actually you are free to use it, but I would say that don’t use Bootstrap or other frameworks, do it with pure HTML and CSS so you can advance your knowledge more than just using a premade code.</p><hr class="post-hr"><h1 id="What-I-learned"><a href="#What-I-learned" class="headerlink" title="What I learned?"></a>What I learned?</h1><p>I learned so many things from this challenge. I have nearly a full knowledge of HTML and CSS, learned new techniques like Flexbox and CSS Grid, making animations, pseudo classes in CSS, using JS libraries in projects and more. I even learned how to make sites responsive to all devices which is so important to know. Two things that I learned after finishing the challenge were SASS/SCSS and Git, which are two important tools to have at your disposal. 💪 I might even go over the codes of some of the sites in the challenge and turn the CSS into SASS if I have time just to practice more in the future.</p><hr class="post-hr"><h1 id="Feedback-Feedback-Feedback"><a href="#Feedback-Feedback-Feedback" class="headerlink" title="Feedback! Feedback!! Feedback!!!"></a>Feedback! Feedback!! Feedback!!!</h1><div class="pic-center"><br><img src="https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/1000/1*c-DaSmO0EV1XawPDC3_TcA.jpeg" alt="Feedback and always feedback :D"><br>Feedback and always feedback :D<br></div><p>One thing that helps me the most while making a website is to post it somewhere like a Facebook group and you’ll get tons of feedback from fellow Developers in order to further improve my site. This challenge’s Facebook group is no exception, it has a community which is awesome!! I basically post a site, write a small description about what technologies I used, what I learned, what needs to be improved and even more. What I get? Many and many feedback from the community. You should be aware that you will probably get many constructive feedback as well as positive feedback, which both helps to make that site better, fix bugs etc. I get good feedback about how cool is that site, I should fix this or improve that etc. 😎</p><p>I have to mention that I’m not the only one that took the challenge. There are many other people that are doing it and as they are dedicating their time to check my sites and provide feedback, it’s important and I have to provide feedback for their projects too. I even ask some questions about how they did that ‘something’ and learn how to do it too. It’s so cool. I recommend checking other fellow developers’ sites and provide feedback to their websites and, who knows, maybe you will learn something from their site too! It’s a win-win.</p><hr class="post-hr"><h1 id="What-I-made"><a href="#What-I-made" class="headerlink" title="What I made?"></a>What I made?</h1><p>After talking about the challenge itself, I should say a few words about the projects or sites that I made too. It’s cool to have nearly 30 projects or websites on your portfolio, some of them aren’t that good, some of them are awesome though (for me!!). I posted some of the awesome ones on my <a href="http://kkasbarian.com" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><strong>portfolio</strong></a> and also few of those awesome ones are below:</p><ul><li><a href="http://www.kkasbarian.com/30Days30Sites/Photographer/index.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><strong>Photography Website</strong></a></li><li><a href="http://www.kkasbarian.com/30Days30Sites/Beverage/index.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><strong>Beverage Site</strong></a></li><li><a href="http://www.kkasbarian.com/30Days30Sites/Fashion-Site/index.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><strong>Fashion Site</strong></a></li><li><a href="http://www.kkasbarian.com/30Days30Sites/Digital-Agency/index.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><strong>Digital Agency Website</strong></a> (The best one that I made ❤️)</li></ul><p>I even have a webpage where I already put all my projects for this challenge there. You can check it out from <a href="http://www.kkasbarian.com/30Days30Sites/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><strong>here</strong></a>.</p><p>I host all the projects on GitHub, you can check the repo of the projects from <a href="https://github.com/KKasbarian/30Days30Sites" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><strong>here</strong></a>. All projects have a README file that describe some info regarding a project or what have I learned from that project.</p><hr class="post-hr"><h1 id="Conclusion"><a href="#Conclusion" class="headerlink" title="Conclusion:"></a>Conclusion:</h1><p>As a final note, this challenge really helped me to improve my knowledge and learn more as I got through the challenges. This is not the end of the journey though. I’ll still learn many things and build more websites and who knows, I might even get a job soon for all the knowledge that I have. I recommend to take this challenge if you want to build websites and further improve your Front-End knowledge!!</p><p><strong>Thanks for reading this post. If you liked it, please leave a comment and share with your friends and family if they want to improve their knowledge too.</strong><br><br></p><p></p><p>Share this post:</p><p></p><div class="flex-share-btn"><br>    <div class="fb-share-button" data-href="http://blog.kkasbarian.com/2018/02/my-journey-of-the-30days30sites-challenge/" data-layout="button_count" data-size="small" data-mobile-iframe="true"><a class="fb-xfbml-parse-ignore" target="_blank" href="https://www.facebook.com/sharer/sharer.php?u=http%3A//blog.kkasbarian.com/2018/02/my-journey-of-the-30days30sites-challenge/">Share</a></div><br>    <div><a class="twitter-share-button" href="https://twitter.com/intent/tweet" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Tweet</a></div><br>    <div><a class="twitter-follow-button" data-show-count="false" href="https://twitter.com/KourkenK" target="_blank" rel="noopener"> Follow @KourkenK</a></div><br></div>]]></content>
    
    <summary type="html">
    
      
      
        &lt;div class=&quot;flex-share-btn&quot;&gt;&lt;br&gt;    &lt;div class=&quot;fb-share-button&quot; data-href=&quot;http://blog.kkasbarian.com/2018/02/my-journey-of-the-30days30sit
      
    
    </summary>
    
      <category term="Web Development" scheme="http://blog.kkasbarian.com/categories/Web-Development/"/>
    
      <category term="HTML" scheme="http://blog.kkasbarian.com/categories/Web-Development/HTML/"/>
    
      <category term="CSS" scheme="http://blog.kkasbarian.com/categories/Web-Development/CSS/"/>
    
      <category term="JavaScript" scheme="http://blog.kkasbarian.com/categories/Web-Development/JavaScript/"/>
    
      <category term="Portfolio" scheme="http://blog.kkasbarian.com/categories/Portfolio/"/>
    
    
      <category term="HTML" scheme="http://blog.kkasbarian.com/tags/HTML/"/>
    
      <category term="CSS" scheme="http://blog.kkasbarian.com/tags/CSS/"/>
    
      <category term="JavaScript" scheme="http://blog.kkasbarian.com/tags/JavaScript/"/>
    
      <category term="Portfolio" scheme="http://blog.kkasbarian.com/tags/Portfolio/"/>
    
      <category term="Web Development" scheme="http://blog.kkasbarian.com/tags/Web-Development/"/>
    
      <category term="Front-End" scheme="http://blog.kkasbarian.com/tags/Front-End/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>How I Started My Web Development Journey</title>
    <link href="http://blog.kkasbarian.com/2017/09/my-web-dev-journey/"/>
    <id>http://blog.kkasbarian.com/2017/09/my-web-dev-journey/</id>
    <published>2017-09-27T12:30:00.000Z</published>
    <updated>2018-02-05T14:12:42.894Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<div class="flex-share-btn"><br>    <div class="fb-share-button" data-href="http://blog.kkasbarian.com/2017/09/my-web-dev-journey/" data-layout="button_count" data-size="small" data-mobile-iframe="true"><a class="fb-xfbml-parse-ignore" target="_blank" href="https://www.facebook.com/sharer/sharer.php?u=http%3A%2F%2Fblog.kkasbarian.com%2F2017%2F09%2Fmy-web-dev-journey%2F&amp;src=sdkpreparse">Share</a></div><br>    <div><a class="twitter-share-button" href="https://twitter.com/intent/tweet" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Tweet</a></div><br>    <div><a class="twitter-follow-button" data-show-count="false" href="https://twitter.com/KourkenK" target="_blank" rel="noopener"> Follow @KourkenK</a></div><br></div><p>Read Time: 7 min read</p><p>Web Development and Programming in general is hard, but millions of people learn to code everyday. The salary is high, lot of companies and startups want different kind of developers for their businesses, be it Front-End, Back-End, QA, Full-Stack or even AI specialists which means the demand for this profession is high.</p><p>I’m a Tech, Android and Computers enthusiast for over 5 years, so I spend lot of time reading and checking many articles, tutorials and even videos about the latest Tech news, new applications and games, smart devices, you name it…</p><p>As months and years passes, I become closer and more interested in Tech in general. And with all these I was also reading some articles about coding, websites, how-to’s, etc…</p><hr class="post-hr"><p>Fast-Forward some years and it was late Spring, or mid May to be specific, May 10–20 2016 to be even more exact than I was! It was the time when my inner me knew that I should go into the path of Web Development as I was struggling at college with another profession which I didn’t like and didn’t learn after, but I had to finish my 3 years of college, even though I won’t look at that profession anymore as I graduated from it at June 2017 (College was from 2015–2017).</p><p>Mid May 2016 was the time I started to dig more about website building and Web Development. I remember I signed up for many major Web Dev learning platform, which includes <a href="https://www.codecademy.com/learn/all" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><strong>Codecademy</strong></a>, <a href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><strong>Free Code Camp (FCC)</strong></a>, <a href="https://www.udemy.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><strong>Udemy</strong></a> and many more tutorials in between 18–21 May (Yes, I remember the dates too!).</p><p>I started to watch videos, reading articles and following the tutorials and steps found on these sites and slowly started to build some simple, not-so-good webpages, which only contained some text, numbers, lists and no styles at all. This means that I was getting the grasp of HTML relatively quickly.</p><div class="pic-center"><br><img src="https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/800/1*C5hvWdJxvLpyl8M1f1FLvA.jpeg" alt="My First Ever Webpage (fairly simple, no styles)"><br>My First Ever Webpage (fairly simple, no styles)<br></div><p>Above you see a so-simple webpage which I was proud of at the time as I was following Codecademy’s tutorial and reached my first ever checkpoint in my first days of the journey.</p><hr class="post-hr"><p>The summer of 2016 was the time which I learned and got good at <strong>HTML</strong> and <strong>CSS</strong>, but was too hard to learn JavaScript as I did follow a few tutorials but I couldn’t feel that I’m getting the hang of it. I couldn’t go further than this, so I got disappointed and felt like it’s not for me. As the last year of college has started, I didn’t have much time to go over it again, so it was a bad time for me from that perspective.</p><p class="quote">“<em>It was really hard for me that I couldn’t go further and let this chance go away, because this was supposed to be the profession of my dreams!</em>”</p><p>Christmas and New Year approached, I had a one-month vacation from college and “that” was the time when I came back to Web Development, to my good hobby, to the Profession that I wanted to do and become a pro at it. Who was my supporter to all this? Myself. It’s not that my family was against it. It’s the opposite, they were completely okay with it, but as they don’t know much about this sites and programming stuff, they were supporting from the “If you can learn it by yourself and you like it, then learn, we’ll be proud of you!” perspective.</p><p>I got excited again and got my hands dirty in code, building some layouts and webpages which were better than the previous ones, but not good compared to real-world websites (I was still a newbie at that time :D ). I’ll list few things that I built following Udemy tutorials:</p><p class="quote"><em><strong>Note:</strong> These websites that are built by me (and also which are awful and beautiful at the same time) are stored locally and <strong>No One</strong> has seen it before, so you are lucky to see all these. I know that newbie developers also have these kind of websites stored privately ;)</em></p><div class="pic-center"><br><img src="https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/1000/1*ETotovfotXeb5JvRcDkEvA.jpeg" alt="Sorry for the harshness of this image. I know that it’s a freaking bad one, it’s rough from all 4 edges but it was my first steps, first but skewed up steps :D"><br>Sorry for the harshness of this image. I know that it’s a freaking bad one, it’s rough from all 4 edges but it was my first steps, first but skewed up steps :D<br></div><div class="pic-center"><br><img src="https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/1000/1*n32r7pY3qc7jJx34w8o4Wg.jpeg" alt="A dumb website done while following an Udemy tutorial (at least learned positioning certain elements to certain places. Also, changed many things myself after tutorial finsihed!)"><br>A dumb website done while following an Udemy tutorial (at least learned positioning certain elements to certain places. Also, changed many things myself after tutorial finsihed!)<br></div><div class="pic-center"><br><img src="https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/800/1*0y_e5tmvXHdq8P-0PSTORg.jpeg" alt="A beautiful Resume, again followed by an Udemy tutorial that’ll hurt your eyes :D"><br>A beautiful Resume, again followed by an Udemy tutorial that’ll hurt your eyes :D<br></div><p>Those were some basic websites that I did by following some tutorials and videos, but I felt like following tutorials could get boring after some time and I read elsewhere that the best way to learn Web Development, Front-End particularly, is to build projects yourself. After 2016–2017 New Year, I didn’t stop, and I’m still working on side projects till now, I learned fully HTML and most of what CSS has to offer and constantly learning what I couldn’t get at first, learned to use some frameworks like Bootstrap, Built-in CSS Grid System and Flexbox (Still learning Grid System), some SASS and LESS (Still learning too), but you noticed that I didn’t mention JavaScript here in the list, that’s because I tried again and I couldn’t get the grasp of it again, but this time I didn’t quit and focused on the above mentioned tools.</p><p>After nearly a year since I got my hands inside coding, again early May to be exact, I felt like I need to show myself to the world that I’m a Front-End Web Developer and have my online presence and learn new things constantly. I started by making a LinkedIn profile for myself, adding a Bio in most of my Socials related to my profession, but something was missing, like, where should people go to see my works and how other people show their works and impress their future boss? The answer is, having a <strong>Portfolio Website</strong>.</p><p>I thought about building a portfolio website for myself by myself to show off my works and get people to know more about my experience and skills, also so they can get in touch with me in case they want to hire me or know more about me.</p><hr class="post-hr"><p>The last few months of my college was so hard and exams everywhere, but I wanted badly to build my portfolio, so I made a schedule to do my studies and preparations for exams first and dedicating 30min-1hour daily at nights to get my hands dirty, but this time, not for building dummy websites, but for building my actual real <em><strong>Portfolio!</strong></em> I started nearly at mid May this year and it took me till the end of July, like, nearly 2,5 months with 30min-1hour of code every single day. Finally, I got my Portfolio site up and running online, so that anyone can see it, also I linked it to LinkedIn for ‘professional reasons’. How amazing is that!!! I was so happy about it and through the 2,5 months, I felt that I’m better now designing and building websites than first when I started (which is too normal, tbh). I know that you’re now thinking on how to find and check my portfolio, so here’s the link to my <strong><em><a href="http://kkasbarian.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Portfolio</a></em></strong>.</p><p>Overall, I’m satisfied with how far I came till now but, I won’t stop here though. My main aim is to get the hang of JavaScript which I would like to learn when I schedule an internship for myself and hopefully there will be offers so I go and learn more and more languages after learning JavaScript.</p><p>For now, I’m part of an online challenge where I should build 30 sites based on the prompts of the day. I already completed more than half of them and I’ll hopefully finish all 30 sites in the next coming weeks or at most, months. Here’s the <strong><em><a href="https://kkasbarian.github.io/30Days30Sites/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">site</a></em></strong> where all the projects of this challenge are hosted. I should admit that this challenge has even more strengthened my knowledge of building websites and I can’t wait to reach till the end of this challenge and be happy with the final outcome.</p><div class="pic-center"><br><img src="https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/800/1*UFb9U9tyTJUHZlBnLCiwFQ.jpeg" alt="Front-End Web Development"><br></div><p>As a conclusion, this was a brief summary of what I was up to this last year and how I reached this far in my journey to learn Web Development. I hope to get better and better in the near-future, learn more languages and frameworks, make my dream come true and apply to jobs and work as a Web Developer.</p><hr class="post-hr"><p class="quote"><em><strong>P.S:</strong> If you want a <strong>Website</strong> for yourself or for your company, startup etc. or you can provide an opportunity for an <strong>Internship</strong> (if you’re based in Armenia), feel free to send me a message from my personal website’s form and I’ll be more than happy to work with you. I’ll get in touch with you in less than a day.</em></p><hr class="post-hr"><p>Thanks for reading my first post, which was about my journey to become a Web Developer. If you reached this far, then I wish you all the success in your profession whatever you have chosen and never give up because you should do all your best, be patient and work hard if you want to achieve your goals, learn a profession and be successful at it. I wish you all the best. Have a good day.</p><p><strong>If you liked my first post, I’ll be happy if you share this or provide some comments so I get more motivated and write more articles about my journey. Thanks for your support, I can’t wait to write more articles!</strong><br><br></p><p></p><p>Share this post:</p><p></p><div class="flex-share-btn"><br>    <div class="fb-share-button" data-href="http://blog.kkasbarian.com/2017/09/my-web-dev-journey/" data-layout="button_count" data-size="small" data-mobile-iframe="true"><a class="fb-xfbml-parse-ignore" target="_blank" href="https://www.facebook.com/sharer/sharer.php?u=http%3A%2F%2Fblog.kkasbarian.com%2F2017%2F09%2Fmy-web-dev-journey%2F&amp;src=sdkpreparse">Share</a></div><br>    <div><a class="twitter-share-button" href="https://twitter.com/intent/tweet" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Tweet</a></div><br>    <div><a class="twitter-follow-button" data-show-count="false" href="https://twitter.com/KourkenK" target="_blank" rel="noopener"> Follow @KourkenK</a></div><br></div>]]></content>
    
    <summary type="html">
    
      
      
        &lt;div class=&quot;flex-share-btn&quot;&gt;&lt;br&gt;    &lt;div class=&quot;fb-share-button&quot; data-href=&quot;http://blog.kkasbarian.com/2017/09/my-web-dev-journey/&quot; data-lay
      
    
    </summary>
    
      <category term="Web Development" scheme="http://blog.kkasbarian.com/categories/Web-Development/"/>
    
      <category term="HTML" scheme="http://blog.kkasbarian.com/categories/Web-Development/HTML/"/>
    
      <category term="CSS" scheme="http://blog.kkasbarian.com/categories/Web-Development/CSS/"/>
    
      <category term="Portfolio" scheme="http://blog.kkasbarian.com/categories/Portfolio/"/>
    
    
      <category term="HTML" scheme="http://blog.kkasbarian.com/tags/HTML/"/>
    
      <category term="CSS" scheme="http://blog.kkasbarian.com/tags/CSS/"/>
    
      <category term="Portfolio" scheme="http://blog.kkasbarian.com/tags/Portfolio/"/>
    
      <category term="Web Development" scheme="http://blog.kkasbarian.com/tags/Web-Development/"/>
    
      <category term="Front-End" scheme="http://blog.kkasbarian.com/tags/Front-End/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
</feed>
